Oh dream We will go galloping away
Oh Dream　駈け出してくよ
Yes, further still
さぁ　もっと遠くへ
Have a little courage, it’ll take you forward
ちいさな勇気抱いて進むんだ
It is limitless, my way
果てしないMy way
On the road home where nothing is going right and you have become disheartened
上手くいかなくて落ち込んだ帰り道で
you happen to notice that only if you run away now you will be fleeing your dreams
ふと気づく　もし今逃げたなら　夢も逃げてゆく
If you start to run, saying quietly that you will not give up
あきらめないと　呟いて走り出せば
the winds of tomorrow will blow and dry your tears
明日の風が吹いて　涙なんて乾かしてくよ
If you should tread down this path you have chosen
選んだ道　歩み出したら
you will not regret it
弱音なんてはかないよ
You will trust in your own course
自分の軌跡信じる
and maintain your potential for all time
可能性とは　無限のはずさ
Oh dream you will run clear through it
Oh Dream　駆け抜けてくよ
then look only forward
そう　前だけを見て
If you overcome that great wall, the radiance is waiting
大きな壁超えたら　輝きが待ってる
Oh dream take it a step at a time
Oh Dream　一歩ずつでも
for we absolutely will not stop
絶対　止まらないから
You surely are drawing nearer to your dream
必ず夢に近づく
Let us go to our future of promise
約束の未来へ行こう
On the other side of the barriers of your unease there is a tomorrow
不安の壁の向こうには明日がある
Your familiar voice is calling out if I should have such a thought
聞きなれた君の声　呼んでいる　そんな気がしたら
You can hear it coming in; now we’re getting somewhere!
着信の音　響いてる　通じてるね！
If you speak truly of your troubles, your heart will become clear
ほんとうの悩みを話したらココロ晴れてく
Now with you I swear
誓い合うよ　いま君と
that place we saw which goes as far as our dreams
夢にまで見たあの場所
A stage where light shines
光輝くstage
Then surely let us go flapping our wings together
きっと一緒に羽ばたいていこう
Oh dream look at that same sky
Oh Dream　同じ空見て
We run out of breath
そう　息を切らして
Sharing until it hurts and our bond grows stronger
痛みまで　分かち合い　強くなった絆
Oh dream one day, our tears
Oh Dream　いつか涙は
will surely become our power
きっと　力になるね
And once you have wiped the tears from your face
泣き顔　拭いたあとの
then let us go forth with the greatest of smiles
最高の笑顔で行こう
This sight, unseen by anyone alone
一人では見れなかったこの景色を
we have wished to see all along; so stop time…
ずっと見てたい　時間を止めて…
Oh dream We will go galloping away
Oh Dream　駈け出してくよ
Yes, further still
さぁ　もっと遠くへ
Have a little courage, it’ll take you forward without becoming lost
ちいさな勇気抱いて進むんだ　迷わずに
Oh dream take it a step at a time
Oh Dream　一歩ずつでも
for we absolutely will not stop
絶対　止まらないから
You surely are drawing nearer to your dream
必ず夢に近づく
Let us go to our future of promise
約束の未来へ行こう
For it is because of today that tomorrow shines
明日は今日より輝くから